2-surf.net 2008-05-02

# Cosmetics,Fragrance,Handbags,Jewelry,Shoes,Music,Art,Music,Automotive,WebTools

|  Home  
  
---|---  
  
---|---  
|    

|  Recent Listings  
---  
  
  [ ** _1º TV FOR RICH & FAMOUS_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Family/Entertainment/12-47-0-18454-0-0.html) \- Other, New York 

  Theresa Bernabe TV, the first international luxury television on internet dedica

  (12-11-2006)

  [ ** _Clean Spam_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Computer-&-Electronics/Computer-Support/9-36-0-21257-0-0.html) \- Australia, Alabama 

  Clean Spam provides spam removal service for all businesses. We are specialists 

  (01-28-2007)

  [ ** _French abroad_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Education/Languages/10-42-0-14348-0-0.html) \- Other, Other 

  Intensive French for non-speakers school in Paris, France. Various courses &

  (10-20-2006)

  [ ** _Pocono Earth_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Recreation-&-Leisure/Outdoors/24-99-0-23526-0-0.html) \- USA, Pennsylvania 

  Free recreational locations in the Pocono Mountains PA. Hiking, Hunting, fishing

  (03-06-2007)

  [ ** _gts_**](http://www.2-surf.net/ArtPhotoMusic/Music/2-5-0-16213-0-0.html) \- Other, Other 

  Dedicated to Ludwig van Beethoven, the site offers the reader detailed informati

  (11-05-2006)

  [ ** _Sabamasoft_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Home-&-Garden/Kitchen/18-82-0-8357-0-0.html) \- USA, 

  This BathroomAccesories common description appears at the end of every Category 

  (10-20-2006)  

2-Surf.net's and 2-surf.com's Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Statement_**  
2-Surf.net and 2-surf.com respects the privacy of our listers. The information we collect about our listers is used by our company only. We retain the data we collect for our business practices only. Our purpose for collecting data is to complete transactions, enhance our site and product offerings, and maintain and secure our site. The types of data we collect are characteristics such as website information, company name and information, email address, passive activity such as pages visited, and physical address, phone number, and purchase information. Users can access all information by logging onto their account.

**_Specific Data Collected_**  
This privacy policy declares collected data in groups. This policy contains 3 data groups. The manner in which data is collected and used is described for each group in the following descriptions.

_Data Group: Web Access Log_  

The following information is collected:

  * ClickStream Information 
  * HTTP Protocol Information 

Data is collected from all Web users in access logs.

The collected data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Website/system administration 
  * Research and Development 

We are the only entity having access to the data

The data is retained untill listing is removed

_Data Group: Purchase Transaction_  

The following information is collected:

  * User's Name 
  * User's business Contact Information 
  * Purchase Information 

Data is collected in order to process your purchase.

The collected data will be used for completion of current activity

We are the only entity having access to the data

The data is retained untill listing is removed

_Data Group: Privacy Policy Info_  

The following information is collected:

  * Business/Organization Name 
  * Address of Business/Organization 
  * Contact Information for the Business/Organization 

Information is collected to allow us to insert information into your privacy policy.

The collected data will be used for completion of current activity

We are the only entity having access to the data

Information is retained according to our stated business practices.

**_Data Security_**  
2-Surf.net and 2-surf.com uses secure encryption technology (secure socket connection) for all sensitive financial information transmitted on our site. Our company has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. 

**_Links and Advertisements_**  
Our website contains links to your sites. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies that require any of our data for any reason. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any web sites having ads or links on our listings. Please review the privacy policy of those sites to understand the implications of providing information to them.

**_Visitors Under 13 Years of Age_**  
2-Surf.net and 2-surf.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from a child under 13 since our site is not directed at children. 

**_Changes to the Privacy Statement_**  
The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. If we significantly change our policy, we will post a notice in a conspicuous place on our website notifying visitors of policy changes. 

**_Cookies_**  
2-Surf.net and 2-surf.com does use cookies for loging into your accounts. 

**_Data Retention Statement_**  
We keep information about your business purchases for 1 year if you purchase a upgrade.

**_Contact Information_**  
Using the following information, you can contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy.  

**_Resolving Privacy Policy Disputes_**  
If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, it can be resolved in the following manner. 

**_Legal Disclaimer_**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**2-Surf.net's and 2-surf.com's Privacy Policy**   

|  Help  
---  
  
    Welcome! Use this window to get help and other useful notes on how to achieve the best results while working with the system.  

Featured Listings  
---  
  
  [ ** _Insurance Broker Finder UK_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Insurance/Car-Insurance/19-137-0-29558-0-0.html) \- United Kingdom, Idaho 

  This website has listed every uk insurance broker from scotland and ireland to w

  [ ** _SafeGuard World International Managed Payroll_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Business/Business-To-Business/5-18-0-29510-0-0.html) \- United Kingdom, Alabama 

  SafeGuard World provide managed payroll and HR solutions to a range of industrie

  [ ** _The Cellular One_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Commerce/Telephone-Services/8-33-0-14132-0-0.html) \- USA, Kansas 

  Compare Cell Phones, Research Cellular phones, Free cell phones, Compare Cell Ph

  [ ** _Felix-Enterprises_**](http://www.2-surf.net/ClothingApparel/Women's/7-28-0-15764-0-0.html) \- USA, Oregon 

  We carry hot lingerie and sexy intimate. FREE shipping on all orders over $50.00

  [ ** _Phone Shop Finder_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Commerce/Telephone-Services/8-33-0-29559-0-0.html) \- United Kingdom, Arkansas 

  This website is a large directory of all UK phone shops and mobile phone shops. 

  [ ** _Photographer Erik Hagman_**](http://www.2-surf.net/ArtPhotoMusic/Photo/2-6-0-29529-0-0.html) \- USA, New York 

  Photographer Erik Hagman, Cars, Still-Life and Landscape Photography.  

Top Listings  
---  
  
  [ ** _drugstores4u.com_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Health-&-Beauty/Pharmaceuticals/17-73-0-2222-0-0.html) \- Canada, 

  FDA approval drugs online, the cheapest prescription Tramadol, fioricet, ultram,

  ( **16767** Hits since 10-19-2006)

  [ ** _BestgenericPharmacy_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Health-&-Beauty/Pharmaceuticals/17-73-0-9799-0-0.html) \- USA, 

  generic pharmacy online offers you the finest quality generic drugs for a very c

  ( **16467** Hits since 10-20-2006)

  [ ** _bestgenericpharmacy_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Health-&-Beauty/Pharmaceuticals/17-73-0-2809-0-0.html) \- USA, 

  Order generic Viagra and other prescription drugs online, online generic pharmac

  ( **12809** Hits since 10-20-2006)

  [ ** _PillHunt_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Sports-&-Fitness/Exercise-&-Health/26-102-0-2305-0-0.html) \- USA, 

  Weightloss comparison and general fitness information at Pillhunt.com

  ( **6826** Hits since 10-20-2006)

  [ ** _genericsmed_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Health-&-Beauty/Pharmaceuticals/17-73-0-15787-0-0.html) \- United Kingdom, Other 

  Buy Generic Viagra, Cialis, Propecia, Levitra online. Guaranteed Cheap,Confident

  ( **5834** Hits since 10-29-2006)

  [ ** _Cheap Web Design_**](http://www.2-surf.net/Web-Services/Web-Design/28-119-0-19105-0-0.html) \- United Kingdom, Alabama 

  Cheap inexpensive website design, SEO and Marketing based in scotland UK. Low pr

  ( **3950** Hits since 12-21-2006)  

© 2001-2008 [ 2-surf.net ](http://www.2-surf.net/) All Rights Reserved. 

All logos and trademarks in this site are property of their respective owners.
